Mohamad Rafly Fajriansyah

Designer/Developer

Bandung, Indonesia



+62 815-2382-8416 raflyzxd@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/raflyfajriansyah https://raflyweb.netlify.app

I am a fresh Information Systems graduate with a Bachelor's degree from the Indonesian Computer University, passionate about learning new things. I enjoy working on designing website interfaces, mobile apps, logos, brands, and posters using Figma, Illustrator, and Photoshop. I also have experience with JavaScript, React.js, Laravel, and PHP through college projects and i'm excited about developing my skills in creating 3D models with Blender.

Work Experience

Telkom Indonesia - Bandung

Aug 2023 – Dec 2023

UI/UX Specialist Internship

- Create 5 project virtual reality user interface and also a smarteye website user interface, give the user 75% a better experience using VR, and bring a better, more eye-catching smarteye website.
- Collaborate with the team to craft a streamlined VR user flow for enhanced user experience clarity.
- Develop a comprehensive design system for each virtual reality (VR) application and website.

Digital Talent Scholarship - Work From Anywhere

Jun 2023 - Sep 2023

UX Designer Training | FGA DTS Kominfo x Google

- Develop and evolve visual brand identities for 2 projects, ensuring consistency across all materials.
- Defining the idea is a crucial first step in the creative process, laying the foundation for clear communication and effective execution.
- Prototyping is an integral part of the design process, allowing for the tangible representation of ideas and concepts.

FundEx.id – Work From Anywhere

Jun 2023 – Jul 2023

UI/UX Designer | Rakamin Virtual Internship Program

- Studying UX (User Experience) involves delving into the intricate interplay between design and human interaction.
- Revamping Fundex's landing page initiates a focused effort to elevate its visual appeal and user experience, aiming about 70% engaging online presence.
- Crafting the Fundex landing page redesign portfolio documents the creative process and highlights the enhanced 80% visual elements and improved user experience, showcasing a compelling transformation.

Education

Universitas Komputer Indonesia - Bandung

2020 - 2024

Bachelor Degree in Information System, GPA: 3.61/4.00

- Learn about programming languages such as JavaScript, PHP, Java, C#, and others.
- Basic database management, adept with SQL and fundamental systems for effective data handling.
- Skilled in information systems project management for successful planning and execution.

Skill & Achivements

- Hard Skills: Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Laravel, React JS, and Blender
- Soft Skills: Creative and efficient, Strong coordination skills, and Excellent time management for tight deadlines
- Certifications (2024): Junior Web Programmer from BNSP
- Certifications (2024): UI/UX Specialist Internship at Telkom Indonesia from Kampus Merdeka Program batch 5
- Certifications (2023): UX Google Design Digitals Talent Fresh Graduate Academy Scholarship Program
- Achievements (2023): One of the 50 best participants out of thousands of registered participants in UX Design training